 
 QUOTATION TO, Customer: XXXXXX Address: XXXXX GST No: XXXXX Contact Name: XXXX Contact No.: XXXX Quotation No.: 121 Date 12/03/2026 Enquiry Refernce By Mail / By Call Contact Person Mr. B. T. Kadam / M r. Suraj Dubal Mail ID n iit004@gmail.com Contact Number +91 9860186056 / 7875154431 / 8600508524 Dear Sir, This is reference to discussion with you; we are pleased to quote our best competitive Price for Inspection . Sr. No. Description of Services SAC Code Qty Unit Price Amount 01 Ultrasonic Testing Charges / Liquid Penetrant Testing Charges / Magnetic Particle Testing Charges / RTFI Charges / NDE Consultancy Charges / Custom 988346/ 988393 10 Per 150.00 1500.00 02 Transportation Charges NA 10 Per 150.00 1500.00 03 Lodging Charges NA 10 Per 150.00 1500.00 04 Boarding Charges NA 10 Per 150.00 1500.00 05. Minimum Visit Charges: NA / custom 06. GST: 18 % on total charge. 07. Payment terms: Immediate after completion of inspection &amp; before submission of reports. 08. Material handling is in yours scope. 09. NDE Level II personnel is in ours scope . 10. Machines is in our scope / yours scope. 11. Consumables is in our scope / yours scope . We trust the above notice is quite competitive acceptable to you Looking forward to favorable reply &amp; confirmed order on us. Your faithfully Mr. Bajirao T. Kadam ASNT Level III (RT, UT, MT, PT, VT) 671830 839470 0 Competent Person under Factory Act 1948 National Industrial Inspection &amp; Training Baramati +91 7875154431, 9860186056 
