 
 QUOTATION TO, Customer: XXXXXX Address: XXXXX GST No: XXXXX Contact Name: XXXX Contact No.: XXXX Quotation No.: 121 Date 12/03/2026 Enquiry Refernce By Mail / By Call Contact Person Mr. B. T. Kadam / Mr. Suraj Dubal Mail ID n iit004@gmail.com Contact Number +91 9860186056 / 7875154431 / 8600508524 Dear Sir, This is reference to discussion with you; we are pleased to quote our best competitive Price for Inspection . Sr. No. Description of Services Level SAC Code Qty Unit Price Amount 01 PT NDE / MT NDE / UT NDE / RTFI NDE / VT NDE / ET NDE / MFL NDE / CUSTOM I / II 988393 10 Per 150.00 1500.00 02 Transportation Charges NA NA 10 Per 150.00 1500.00 03 Lodging Charges NA NA 10 Per 150.00 1500.00 04 Boarding Charges NA NA 10 Per 150.00 1500.00 05. Minimum Candidates required for campus training : 5 / custom 06. Training will be conducted as per yours written practice . 0 7 . In addition to the course fee, as stated above 18% GST will be applicable. 0 8 . Course fee include s study material, exam fee, certificate fee. 09 . Payment terms: Immediate after completion of training &amp; submission of certificates . We trust the above notice is quite competitive acceptable to you Looking forward to favorable reply &amp; confirmed order on us. Your faithfully Mr. Bajirao T. Kadam ASNT Level III (RT, UT, MT, PT, VT , ET, MFL ) 676275 838200 0 0 Competent Person under Factory Act 1948 National Industrial Inspection &amp; Training Baramati +91 7875154431, 9860186056 
